GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
EPISODE 12
I see you're happy.
Yes, I'm glad. I'm very, very happy.
Even...
won't you say anything?
"Cool", "I'm delighted" -
at least something like that.
Of course it was cool!
How much?
Wow so much.
Come on. Badly?
That much?
Wow. Yes, it was very cool.
Can I sing for Sol,
when will you be back?
To make her fall in love.
Do you want to make me fall in love with songs?
Certainly.
And also...
I want at least once...
perform on stage again.
Did you like it?
Maybe I really liked it, or maybe...
I realized what awaits me
in the future - I don’t know.
But one thing I'm sure of -
my heart began to pound.
Here you go. What did I say?
And one more thing.
Look. Dali after the performance.
This is CEO Kim's business card, right?
And what is he?
Well...
Said he wanted to pick up the Eclipse
to your agency.
Is it true?
How nice, Sung Jae! Great!
Are you so happy?
Certainly.
You can't imagine how worried I was,
that I'm disturbing you.
Don't be stupid.
You know, Sung Jae...
There is nothing more to dream of.
Really?
I wish...
time passed more slowly.
The trees have already bloomed.
Sorry.
Where's my dad?
A detective has been brought to you.
The last chamber is around the corner.
Dad...
Are you crying?
I just yawned.
Wow! Dad? I didn't notice you.
Are you standing and mourning your father?
I? When did this happen?
I came here on business
how did you end up here?
Here's a dreamer. He got worried and came running.
They called me and said
that a person is dying.
I came running!
I have 20 stitches on my forehead...
and a couple of bruises on the neck.
Your dad is Captain Immortality,
just know that.
What other Captain?
Not even an officer.
Tell me what happened?
Murder suspect
at the Juyang Reservoir
They arrested him and are now taking him to the police station.
The detainee managed to escape
from the police and now...
Lord, Lord, what's going on.
It's good that he was caught.
This is not a person.
Kim is wanted throughout the country
judicial authorities are involved.
Broken? Dad, there's something wrong with the door.
What? Leave it, we'll figure it out later.
Dad is watching the news now.
The approximate height of the criminal is 180 cm,
Eye color - brown, strong build.
- If you see him...
- Kim Young Soo?
-...let me know immediately.
On the screen you now see
photo of the criminal.
If you notice him,
report to the police.
The suspect's name is Kim Young Soo.
We urge Kim's victims
contact immediately
to law enforcement agencies.
Murder suspect
at the reservoir.
Kim Young Soo.
Dad will catch Kim Young Soo soon,
That's all!
What? Will he come here?
Yes. May 10.
Will you be able to keep watch somewhere nearby?
10th? What will happen?
Are you afraid that he will come for you?
He won't go where he was caught
red-handed.
Maybe...
...and he will climb.
Salt, don't worry
Everything is done for your safety.
Talk to your family.
Maybe you should move away for a while.
Will it be better this way?
If Kim Young Soo notices the detectives,
they won't catch him.
It's not about my experiences.
Yeon Soo needs to be detained.
What are you...
are you thinking of luring him here?
No way. It's dangerous.
You're just about to grab it.
- What... What are you planning?
- I really want to explain to you,
what's going on, but I really can't.
Please don't ask anything
but just...
...help.
Consider yourself protecting me.
That's the only way...
you will catch him.
What happened that day?
She said, think only about yourself.
All this happened because of your stupidity!
Don't notice me. And don't worry.
Wherever I am, whatever I do
and no matter what happens...
Forget me, Sung Jae. Please...
Whatever happens, Sol...
I won't leave you alone.
Why don't you ask for help?
Geum!
My God. How cute!
- Hyun Joo!
- Geum!
I missed you!
I miss you too! Very, very strong!
Hyun Joo! Hyun Joo! Hyun Joo! Hyun Joo!
Yes, Sung Jae!
Hyun Joo! How are you?
Horror. Did you eat something wrong?
Why did you jump into the water?
- What are you, Non Ge?
- No.
I just saw Sol coming here.
And I got scared.
Has she already passed?
We were saved.
Well, here it is, my treasure.
What would you do without me?
And don't talk.
You are my only one, princess.
Wait...
We were completely wet.
It's cold, right?
Shall we hug? Shall we hug?
Cold.
Very cold.
- Do you have a pair?
- Not anymore. It was cancelled.
They should have told us earlier. Textbooks are hard.
Let's.
Let's go.
Mother! Grandmother!
Lim Geum!
Is there anyone at home?
I'll come in.
Wait here. I'll take the textbooks.
Let's see.
What? It is forbidden!
There's nothing to see here, that's it.
I'm interested.
What kind of room does Lim Sol have?
It's not always such a mess here.
I usually clean up.
Not quite tight.
We need to put up a grate.
What?
Is the window closing?
Yes, sure.
Close it at night.
Further. Where's your stun gun?
- Come here.
- What?
- This?
- Yes.
Put it under your pillow.
What's wrong with you?
Suddenly someone comes up to you.
Gorgeous.
Do you know such words?
Who will come to me?
Who's there?
Sol has a liberal arts background.
They were cancelled. What to do?
Sit here. I'm on a reconnaissance mission.
The hair got caught!
Carefully.
So.
Stay here. Don't go out.
Sorry.
He said don't go out!
It seems...
the door was open.
What is it?
- Nobody?
- Nobody.
Let's go out.
So.
It's dangerous here, call the police.
Fine.
- Stand-I-I-I-I-I-yat!
- God!
No!
God!
You?
Scoundrel.
Salt!
How did your tongue turn?
I knew it. Yes. I knew it!
Are you chasing my friend?
No, Sol, it’s me who’s behind him...
What were you doing here?
And Hyun Joo, why are you wearing my clothes?
We fell into the lake and went to change clothes.
Everyone judges for himself!
What about you? What were you doing here?
I helped Sol carry her textbooks.
And just like that, no one was home!
Great!
Have you brought your supplies again?
How many? 300 pieces?
I explained that these are not mine!
He explained! Be silent!
Little sister.
Let's resolve everything peacefully.
I give you permission to meet.
And you give us permission.
Even if you are against...
we don't care.
How do you talk to your older brother?
Since when are you his big brother?
Don't do that, Sol. He's older.
Be more polite.
By... By... More politely?
Wow!
Don't be angry, don't be angry.
Of course, in the whole world
takes care of me
only my princess Hyun Joo!
My treasure.
Why are you in this house
no one respects you?
Shameless!
You're asking for it!
- I can arrange it again!
- Calm down.
- I can’t!
- Take it away.
- What if I don’t clean it up?
- Take it away!
I'll hit!
What an asshole. I told her so many times!
If you don't like it, stop them.
Something goes, something comes.
Everything has a price.
I wouldn't get married -
I wouldn’t see my bunnies.
I don't think I can decide to do this.
Apparently, fate itself brought them together.
If you try and fate doesn't change,
This means it is a conscious choice.
Sometimes we make a decision
already knowing the result.
It suits us.
You are right.
They have the right to choose.
Can I interfere?
They like each other.
They probably like it.
By the way, what about the contract?
In Hyuk hasn't answered me yet.
I can't get through to him.
Did something happen?
I'm worried.
Who cares about whom?
Salt...
you know...
No, forget it.
May 10.
Will you be able to keep watch somewhere nearby?
Maybe...
he will appear.
May 10.
GYMA VIDEO AND DVD
Baek In Hyuk!
What is this?
In Hyuk, were you sitting at home?
Who's there?
- Morning.
- What have you forgotten here?
In Hyuk moved out of here.
Now this is my office. And what?
Hello Sol.
How are you...
Have you moved out of here?
Why suddenly?
He was so upset after the broadcast,
that he went to his home.
- I didn’t know?
- Ether? Which one?
Go crazy.
In Hyuk. Are you crying?
Leave me alone.
I found a girl and completely forgot about my friends.
Yes, love definitely makes you crazy.
Do you know where In Hyuk lives?
Even you don't know. Where am I from?
I know!
I'm the chairman of the fan club!
I even know what color
the roof of his house.
What? Fan club?
And where is this house?
A bit far from us.
How will we go?
By bus? Or should we call a taxi?
Let's go by car. Why bother?
Did you earn money and buy a foreign car?
From salary it is necessary
save money.
God. What a fool you are.
So how? Waste?
So.
This is my Sunny.
Who else is Sunny?
Did you want to show off your car?
Certainly.
Why else would I give you a ride?
God. It still stinks, what should I do?
Damn this idiot.
The toilet was attacked.
In terms of?
What? What's happened? Where is the water?
Why is there no water?
Ended?
Let's see.
And there is nothing here.
It stings! It stings! My God!
Bottle. There is water in the bottle.
Nothing can kill me, okay?
What's happened?
Dad, there's something wrong with the door.
So what should I do?
It stings my eyes!
No no. Definitely not.
I'd rather let my eyes burn.
No no.
How do I get out of here?
Telephone in the room.
Help!
The man was hurt!
God. They make noise and noise.
I can't stand it.
My head is pounding!
- God.
- We need to repair the road.
I'm here!
Help-ee!
Stop barking already, you lousy dog!
Who am I telling?!
So noisy.
Of course, you won't be able to hear me!
Also this dog.
Crap. Damn it.
I'll wait.
Will wait for Song Jae to come back.
Are you mocking? Press the gas!
And if my Sunny trips over a stone
and hit?
In how many months will we arrive?
Why did you take this car?
And what sense?
Here-here.
Koreans are an impatient people.
My heart demands freedom! Admire!
We love each other.
Yes. We were overtaken by a cultivator.
Look. We arrived.
Everything right?
From here you should see the house
with a red roof.
Guys.
Isn't that In Hyuk?
- What's wrong with him?
- Baek In Hyuk!
Baek In Hyuk!
In Hyuk, stand up!
In Hyuk! Baek In Hyuk!
Stand!
"Run!"
- For him!
Son Jae! Son Jae! How are you?
- Everything is fine.
- Baek In Hyuk!
- In Hyuk!
- Stop, In Hyuk!
- Stay there!
Nightmare, nightmare.
I'm holding. Let's go.
What?
What's wrong with you? Let go, let go!
Quiet!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
- Everything is fine?
- Is this what you came back for?
Is this the end of the world?
Move on with your life. Why die?
Who was going to die?
Because of you my favorite circle
carried far away.
They came out of nowhere and made noise!
Damn it, In Hyuk.
God. I would say so. I'm all wet!
- What can I say? You didn't ask.
- No no!
- Look. Look there!
- What? What's there?
No. Sunny!
Sunny! No.
Noooo.
Sunny. No!
No, Sunny, no. No!
Photo for memory.
Guys...
one photo?
Song Jae's father relates to In Hyuk,
like your own son.
I was planning on coming to him
but it didn't work.
Do you like makgeolli?
- Like this.
- Carefully. My God.
The table is modest.
If we had known, we would have been prepared.
Certainly! In Hyuk's friends have arrived
from Seoul, you can't offend them!
No! There are too many dishes here.
A real royal feast.
And yet I feel uneasy.
I'll go catch some chicken.
No need! They will burst like this.
Eat before the chicken is caught.
- Thank you!
Wait. What about your friend?
Come here, I'll pour you some makgeolli!
My God.
Did it suddenly rain?
What's up?
Yes, this is Geum's video.
Yes, Sol.
Where?
Gampo-ri?
Where is this?
Why did you go so far?
And the car somehow ended up in the water, right?
While you live in my house,
I don't allow you to spend the night with a guy!
Son Jae's friend's parents are with us.
If you don't believe me, I'll call them. Should I call?
Okay, no need.
Don't disturb adults, sit quietly.
Behave yourself.
Let's.
That's who it's good for.
Where is he?
Gone?
The water is cold. You'll freeze.
My hands turned red.
Everything is fine.
Head to Seoul.
I wonder how?
My Sunny is now at the bottom of the sea.
Everything is fine.
Why did I take you? Damn it.
By the way, In Hyuk.
Do you let your goats go for walks?
What?
She got out again.
Get up, let's go get Sun Dol.
Sun Dol!
Sun Dol, stop!
Stop! Wait for us. Sun Dol!
Sun Dol, stop. Stop!
Behind her, behind her! Let's run!
Stop! Sun Dol! Crap!
Crap!
Sun Dol! Stop!
Salt!
Salt! How are you?
Everything is fine.
- Sun Dol!
- Quietly, quietly, quietly.
Don't move. Don't move.
Sun Dol, here.
- Come to me. Let's.
- Let's.
- No! No, no, no.
- Come here.
Don't come near! Don't come near!
Got it! Got it!
Finally.
Why do you always run away?
That's great.
Let's go. My God.
Let's go.
Get it! Get it!
Blockheads. They were getting ready to take a shower.
Beautiful.
You wanted...
go to the sea.
Here we are by the sea.
And it's true.
I like.
You're close.
Me too.
Doves!
Are you on a date?
Yes!
Look!
- Follow him.
- Forward.
- Come here!
- Sun Jae!
- Salt.
Don't come near!
- No need, guys.
- We must, we must!
No, really!
- Let's go!
- Come in!
Sink him!
Get it!
Salt!
Are you quitting music?
In Hyuk.
Honestly...
I'm scared.
Will a swimmer turn into a musician?
I chose an unfamiliar path.
I'm scared.
But...
Together we can definitely do it.
I don't know how much time I have left
but the best...
I want the days of my youth...
share with you.
Crap. What are you doing?
Song Jae. Only girls say this.
So you burst into tears here!
- Let me go, let me go, let me go!
- I won’t let you in!
Now you'll strangle me!
So.
Choose.
Here it is.
I see you smiling
and it’s already easier for me.
I was worried that you would be scared
news.
I won't be scared. Everything is fine.
It's strange that you worry about me.
What? Lost it, now do you regret it?
You should have thought earlier, you fool.
The train has left.
And don't talk.
The train has left, yes.
But I told the truth.
I didn't use you.
I know it's late
but I wouldn't want to...
for you to be offended.
Fine. Thanks for saying that.
The most popular liked me
school boy.
Self-esteem rises.
I'm actually a good person.
I know. This is not serious.
You're a good guy.
Finally, at least someone praised me.
Well?
- Did you bring it?
- Yes. Choose.
So. Move over.
Where's my phone?
You called your mom recently.
Yes. It was in my pocket.
Probably fell out somewhere?
You fell while we were chasing the goat.
So he fell out.
Salt! How are you?
Everything is fine.
Maybe!
Let's go.
Don't wait for us.
What?
No. Nothing.
I'll look for it myself. You stay here.
Found it!
Salt?
Salt!
Where is she?
Lim Sol!
Salt!
Lim Sol! Salt!
Lim Sol!
You left without telling me!
Song Jae...
Did something happen?
Did you fall?
What?
Yes. I tripped and lost my balance.
Let's see.
Everything is fine.
What about the ankle?
Doesn't it hurt?
Let's get out of here.
It's starting to get dark. I'm scared.
Let's go.
He told me to stand still.
Why did you go there?
Sorry.
Why are you so worried?
Salt.
Nothing...
don't you want to say?
No. And what?
Just. If something is bothering you,
don't be patient.
Talk to me about it.
It will be easier this way.
Yes.
Fine.
You're lying.
You are silent to protect me.
But Sol...
no matter what you're hiding...
I'll come that day.
This...
my conscious choice.
Let's go.
I'm hungry.
He screamed so much that his voice died down.
What should I do?
Help! Help!
The man feels bad!
How long will I sit here?
I'm dying of hunger.
When will Sun Jae come?
Yes.
Exactly.
I will get out on my own.
I just didn't think
that the window will break.
OK.
We will replace the glass.
What?
Where is everyone?
We're going to catch octopuses.
Approach the pier. You have half an hour.
What? What's there?
They're going to catch octopuses.
Is it true?
Then I'll go get changed.
Do you want to join them?
- What?
- I don't want.
Half an hour has passed, where are they?
Yes. Well then.
I knew it. My God.
So.
Dad, let's set sail! Come on, come on.
- Okay, okay. Give it all here.
- Hold it.
- Forward!
- In terms of? They won't come? I'm leaving!
Quiet, quiet, quiet. Where are you going?
The octopuses are waiting for you.
Let's go back. Like this. Sit down.
Dad, let's set sail!
Buddy! Have a good time!
No! Noooo!
Noooo!
Why didn't you dry your hair?
You'll catch a cold.
I don't know where they have a hairdryer.
Moreover, we are guests.
Here you go.
Eat for now.
Don't look. Eat strawberries.
And I want to.
By the way, I don’t even need balm.
- He's not here.
- You are like a balm for the soul.
And yesterday you were silent.
-Are you, by any chance, the sun?
- And what?
Then why does my heart melt?
It's not funny anymore.
What, isn't it funny?
Are you, by any chance, a chocolate bar?
- Sweet?
- Yes, I guessed it!
- Are you having fun?
- I'm making you laugh.
You like jokes like this.
Will you share?
Sun Dol!
Did you get out again?
Run!
Well, then I'll go to bed.
Where?
To the guest room.
Where they were told to go to bed.
See you tomorrow.
Where...
- ...should I sleep?
- You?
There. Here's a tent.
I'm also a guest.
Song Jae!
And... So what, so what?
Will you sleep with me?
I'm kidding. Kidding.
Good night.
You'll be scared -
...call.
Come on. What's so scary about that?
Salt.
You haven't spent the night in houses like this.
It's scary here at night.
So quiet that every rustle can be heard.
There are also ghosts here.
How's that?
But I'm not afraid of ghosts!
Bye!
What? What's happened?
There's a ghost there, really.
What? Ghost?
Yes. The most real thing.
Didn't you hear anything?
I was very scared.
How to fall asleep?
What are you doing?
Then I'll go there.
What?
Will you sleep with a ghost?
No.
Are you afraid of me?
You heard dad.
I am innocence itself.
And that's how much I respect you.
Not that much.
You came to me because
scared of a ghost?
Yes.
And it's also very cold there. Yes!
Here, look.
The tent is shaking from the cold
in different directions:
here and there.
And there is always a draft there that will blow you away!
My God. I would say so
that you want to lie with me.
You don't know how to lie.
If I tell you now...
...will you let me in?
No.
Here, look.
This is the border. I won't cross it.
How good.
What if you switch?
Have you ever shared a desk?
If you go beyond the line, everything that's yours is mine.
Well done.
So here it is. Don't cross the line.
Aren't you tired?
Lie down.
You have gone abroad.
It turns out that it is so.
So what should I do now?
So you're taking my hand.
I'm picking it up.
Fine. Please.
But how will you take it?
I won't be able to sleep.
It won't work that way.
I'll take all of you.
Fine. That's how we'll fall asleep.
What are those sounds?
These are ghosts. Yes.
How scary!
Salt.
Yes, Sung Jae?
How many are left?
I don't know.
I wish you wouldn't disappear.
If only we could just...
stuck here.
I wish...
tomorrow didn't come.
Maybe break the clock?
Break?
Let's try.
Song Jae.
Yes, Sol?
If suddenly...
tomorrow I...
No...
I'll be back today...
don't be upset.
Fine.
And just don't cry.
I won't.
I like you.
I'll regret...
if I don't say it again.
I like you.
I love you.
I love you, Sol.
This...
my last hope.
What is this?
Help!
Who's there?
Mister Ryu?
Yes!
Yes, it's me!
It's me!
My God. What's happened?
Help. Save me.
I'm stuck here. Save.
Are you stuck in the bathroom?
So what should we do?
Wait, I'll come in now
and I'll open the door.
The door is broken, you won't open it.
Dial 119! 119!
- 119?
- Dial 119! 119!
Didn't you hit yourself?
Mister Ryu!
Mister Ryu! Mister Ryu!
Dial 119, quickly!
- Save me!
- I can knock down the door.
No need to knock down the door!
It is very durable.
Even a strong man
can't knock it out.
- I hurt my shoulder.
- Okay, okay.
- You move further, further away.
- Why do I need all this?
I'm coming in!!!
Everything is fine? Mister Ryu!
Thank you for saving me.
And here is today's dinner.
Goodbye...
...Sunny.
Kim Tae Sun! Come on faster.
Would have stayed another day.
It's time for us to go home.
We'll come again.
Shall we listen to music?
Salt.
Salt?
Did you fall asleep?
Where am I?
What's happened?
And why are you next to me?
Salt!
What's wrong with you?
Did something happen?
Who are you?
Really...
you...
back to the future?
Let go!
- Salt!
- Don't come closer!
I was a little confused.
I have to go. Sorry.
If suddenly...
tomorrow I...
No...
I'll be back today...
don't be upset.
Fine.
And just don't cry.
I won't.
Lim Sol!
Salt!
The future has changed!
Sun Jae, what should we do?
I will change my destiny myself.
Therefore, Sung Jae...
don't come this time.
GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
The main thing is to meet in the future.
That's enough.
I also hope this
not the last time.
Were you together last night?
Song Jae. Where is my daughter now?
So you're back?
Detective Kim, save me.
Do you think Kim Yong Soo might have gone missing?
Maybe the future has changed?
Save!
Salt!
Song Jae...
maybe we shouldn't have met.
Translated and voiced by the studio
"Mobile TV"
commissioned by the online cinema Ivy
in 2024.